Rowan Lin

PROFILE

A marketing specialist with proficiency in web development and data analysis. I am capable with HTML, CSS, and Javascript and knowledgeable with Google Analytics and Ads. My positive energy and diverse background are my greatest strengths.

SKILLS

Advanced Microsoft Excel
HTML, CSS, and Javascript
Google Analytics Certified
Google Ads Certified
Adobe Photoshop
SQL Proficient
Advanced Writing
Great Communication
Creativity

CONTACT INFO

PHONE (213) 705-7484

EMAIL rowanlinoo@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Major in Marketing

University of Texas at Dallas | 2009-2013

EXPERIENCE

ASSISTANT PRODUCER

E&F Production Company | Shanghai, China 2013-2014

- Assisted in Pre-Production responsibilities such as acting as casting assistant and assistant production director
- Translated negotiations for projects between Englishspeaking and Mandarin speaking production teams

FREELANCE WRITER

 Worked freelance writing stories related to the gaming industry including published a weekly serial of stories for gaming communities to engage members

MARKETING ASSOCIATE

B&G Lighting | Changzhou, China 2014-2016

- Discovered, managed and generated leads to break into a new geographical demographic
- Created digital content to promote awareness of products

DOG TRAINER/BOARDING

Self-Employed | Ventura, CA 2016-Present

• Prepared and executed training regimens specifically catered to each individual dog

AWARDS AND ACTIVITIES

Academic Decathlon - 2007-2008

1st Place Team in County Tournament; 1st Place Varsity Essay with 10+ medals in other events such as Math, History, etc. 3rd Place Team in State Tournament

Marketing Director of Circus Club- 2012-2013

Created Flyers and events to attract members. Successfully increased membership 500% during first year.

President of Circus Club - 2013-2014

Delegated responsibilities and maintained enthusiasm

HOBBIES

Soccer: Placed 1st in County Tournaments in High School

Art: Love Graphic Design and Art

Science and Natural History: Enjoy reading scientific

articles and going to the museum

Ultra-light Backpacking and Hiking: Hiked in Nepal, Indonesia, China. Sewed a ultra-light tent under 2lbs.

Dog-Lover: Studied dog behavior and learned scientifically

approved dog-training methods